KYLE WEI

(306) 261-6452 wei.kyle@gmail.com 2421 Clarence Avenue South Saskatoon, SK S7J 1M1 A 2nd year Computer Systems Technology student studying at Saskatchewan Polytechnic. A loyal worker with over 8 years of experience in electronics retail and service environments. Enjoys a variety of sports, outdoor activities, games, and musical performance.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

- » Management of devices and users using Active Directory and SCCM
- » Configuration, installation, and maintenance of network hardware and end-user devices
- » Troubleshooting and resolving hardware, system, and network issues
- » Planning and assembling computer systems and hardware

TRANSFERABLE SKILLS

- » Communicating effectively with co-workers and clients in service environments
- » Identifying, and teaching skill sets to new team members
- » Planning and coordinating with others to host recreational events
- » Fluent in English and Mandarin
- » Level A2 German Proficiency

VOLUNTEER WORK

Technical Mentor

Canada Learning Code, Saskatoon, SK February 29, 2020

» Teens Learning Code: HTML & CSS

Instructor Aide/Tutor

Saskatchewan Polytechnic, Saskatoon, SK Winter 2020

Junior Football Coach, Defensive Line

Centennial Collegiate, Saskatoon, SK Fall 2012, Fall 2013

WORK EXPERIENCE

Systems Technician (Freelance) | Blakley RG Chartered Accountant February 2020 - Present | Saskatoon, SK

- » Managing and maintaining network infrastructure fro a small acounting firm
- » Working with clients to build solutions and provide on-site and remote technical support
- » Implemented automated server backup schedule and installed a new UPS unit and monitoring/automation software
- » Diagnosed and resolved Microsoft Exchange issues stemming from DNS configurations

System Support Technician (Summer Student) | Saskatoon Public Schools June 2019 - August 2019 | Saskatoon, SK

- » Working with other technicians to provide technical support to teachers and support staff
- » Responding to and resolving help desk support tickets via phone, email, and remote desktop
- » Managing client devices and software deployments through SCCM
- » Performing repairs and component replacement on desktop PCs and laptops
- » Maintaining and upgrading network devices throughout the school division
- » Imaging and preparing new laptops for new and returning school division staff
- » Took part in division-wide staff laptop rollouts during the month of June 2019
- » Configured and deployed Cisco VoIP phones to Nutana Collegiate
- » Assembled and installed new server racks, network equipment, and wiring in Nutana Collegiate and North Park Wilson School

Product Process Specialist | Best Buy Canada

July 2015 - Present | Saskatoon, SK

- » Team has been recognized for consistently having the best warehouse in Western Canada, as well as one of the best in the country
- » Designated as the head of department training; in charge of training new employees in position responsibilities and processes
- » Shipping, receiving, stocking, and merchandising of store product
- » Safely transporting and loading large items, such as refrigerators and washing machines

EDUCATION

Saskatchewan Polytechnic

Diploma, Computer Systems Technology Expected Graduation Date: 2020

University of Saskatchewan

Bachelor of Science, Computer Science 2011 - 2017 (Incomplete)

ACTIVITIES & INTERESTS

- » Studied 12 years of piano, with performance and competition experience
- » Played seven seasons on baseball and softball teams, two years of badminton, and attend snowboarding/skiing trips with a group of friends
- » Ran a six month long Dungeons and Dragons campaign and several one-shot sessions with multiple in-person and remote players

WORK EXPERIENCE

Home Entertainment Specialist | Best Buy Canada *August 2012 - August 2014* | Saskatoon, SK

- » Showcasing televisions and home audio systems, demonstrating related features about products to customers, and informing them about store-provided services
- » Arranging customer television orders to the store, and scheduling home service appointments

Gaming Specialist | Best Buy Canada

November 2011 - August 2012 | Saskatoon, SK

- » Showcased video game consoles, games, and provided relevant information on setup and usage of computers, consoles and accessories
- » Explaining the features and differences pertaining to different headphones and portable audio systems
- » Cleaning, organizing and stocking product within assigned department

References available upon request.